pincodes.info 2019-11-06

# Privacy Policy

As used in this policy, "Pincodes.info" refers to all websites (including http://pincodes.info), properties, and services owned or operated by Pincodes.info, Inc. 

This Privacy Policy is part of Pincodes.info's Terms of Use and describes the privacy practices of Pincodes.info. Below you can find information about when and how we collect information from you or concerning your computer or device ("Information"), including Personally Identifiable Information (defined below). 

By visiting the Pincodes.info website, visiting a Pincodes.info client website that provides notice of its use of Pincodes.info and/or this policy, or registering for our service, you acknowledge that you accept and consent to the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies other than Pincodes.info, like google of which maps and ads are served.

 **Information Collected  
**Pincodes.info may also collect certain Information about a visitor's computer that may be furnished by the visitor's browser, such as:   
Browser Information   
Operating System Information  
Mobile Device Information (e.g., device identifier, mobile operating system, etc.)  
IP Address  
Page Accessed   
Geographic Location  
Time of Visit  
Referring Site, Application, or Service  
Name,email,message etc in case of comments

  *   
**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Pincodes.info may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Pincodes.info's sole discretion. Pincodes.info encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
